

#### DEEP LEARNING R&D ENGINEER

22 Square Louis Armand, 35000, Rennes, France

□ (+33) 6-4647-0816 | Marchang@irisa.fr | Archangheng19931123.github.io | Drangheng19931123 | Drangheng19

"Maximum effort!"

### About Me\_\_\_

I am a second year PhD student in <u>LACODAM</u> team at <u>INRIA Rennes</u> laboratory. I am working under the supervision of <u>Prof. Elisa FROMONT</u> and <u>Prof. Sébastien LEFEVRE</u>. In the same time, I work as a Deep learning R&D Engineer at <u>ATERMES</u> in Paris. My current research interest is deep learning for multispectral object detection, small object detection and video object detection.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

ATERMES Paris area, France

DEEP LEARNING R&D ENGINEER

Dec. 2018 - now

- Built Deep Learning models for accurate object detection (car, pedestrian, bicycle, etc) at long distance (>3km).
- Fusing information from multiple sensors (thermal camera & visible camera) to improve the detection precision.
- Model inference acceleration for efficient deep learning applications on embedded systems.

#### **Hubert Curien laboratory**

Saint-étienne, France

APPRENTICESHIP Sep. 2017 - Oct. 2018

- · Implement different deep learning models for face/person detection in public transport (bus, tramway, subway, etc).
- Proposed efficient video object detection methods for video surveillance applications.

## **Education**

INRIA Rennes Rennes, France

PHD STUDENT IN DEEP LEARNING AND COMPUTER VISION

Dec. 2018 - now

- Subject: Multispectral Object detection for all-day video surveillance.
- Industry-oriented PhD program, cooperation with ATERMES company.

**Télécom Saint-étienne**Saint-étienne, France

ENGINEER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER VISION AND IMAGE PROCESSING

Sep. 2015 - Oct. 2018

• One-year Apprenticeship in Hubert Curien laboratory.

Xidian University Xi'an, China

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2016

### **Publications**

#### Multispectral Fusion For Object Detection With Cyclic Fuse-and-refine Blocks [pdf]

Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

27TH IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON IMAGE PROCESSING (ICIP2020)

Oct. 2020

We propose a new feature fusion method for neural networks that leverages the complementary/consistency balance existing in multispectral
features by adding to the network architecture, a particular module that cyclically fuses and refines each spectral feature. We obtain state-ofthe-art results on KAIST Multispectral pedestrian detection benchmark.

### Improving video object detection by Seq-Bbox Matching [pdf]

Prague, Czech Republic

14TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON COMPUTER VISION THEORY AND APPLICATIONS (VISAPP2019)

Feb. 2019

 We propose a novel and highly effective box-level post-processing method to improve the accuracy of video object detection. The proposed method can be applied to online/offline detection. It achieves state-of-the-art performance on ImageNet VID dataset.

AUGUST 30, 2020 HENG ZHANG · RÉSUMÉ 1